A Guide to the Richard Harding Davis Collection 1889-1915, n.d.
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Richard Harding Davis Collection 1889-1915, n.d.
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
6109-f
This holding consists of 33 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This holding was deposited on August 11, 1964.
Contents List
- Letters
  - Richard Harding Davis to Mrs. Brown [June 1, 1889], ALS, 1 p. (Box 15)
  - Richard Harding Davis to [Samuel Sidney] McClure January 11, 1891, ALS, 1 p. (Box 15)
    Attached is a magazine photo of Richard Harding Davis
  - Richard Harding Davis to Mr. [_________] Sinclair [1892], ALS, 4 pp. (Box 15)
  - Richard Harding Davis to C.T. Scott August 30, 1893, ALS, 2 pp. (Box 15)
  - Richard Harding Davis to Augustus Thomas November 15 [1893], ALS, 2 pp. (Box 15)
  - [George ________] to Richard Harding Davis [1895], ALS, 1 p. (Box 15)
  - Henry M[orton] Stanley for Richard Harding Davis February 24, 1899, ALS, 2 pp. (Box 15)
  - Arthur W[ing] Pinero to Richard Harding Davis August 8, 1899, ALS, 4 pp. (Box 15)
  - Arthur W[ing] Pinero to Richard Harding Davis December 17, 1906, ALS, 2 pp. (Box 15)
  - Richard Harding Davis to Mrs. [Brand] Whitlock September 16, 1915, ALS, 6 pp. (Box 15)
  - Richard Harding Davis to [Richard Watson] Gilder February 13, n.y., ALS, 2 pp. (Box 15)
  - Richard Harding Davis to [_______] March 5, n.y., ALS, 1 p. (Box 15)
  - Richard Harding Davis to Albert [_______] April 17, n.y., ALS, 1 p. (Box 15)
  - Richard Harding Davis to [_______] Moffett August 13, n.y., ALS, 1 p. (Box 15)
  - Richard harding Davis to William Morton Payne August 23, n.y., ALS, 2 pp. with transcript (Box 15)
  - Richard Harding Davis to James P. Munroe October 5, n.y., ALS, 2 pp. (Box 15)
  - Richard Harding Davis ot [______] Bridges October 18, n.y., ALS, 1 p. (Box 15)
  - Richard Harding Davis to E.S. Goodhue November 12, n.y., ALS, 2 pp. (Box 15)
  - Arthur W[ing] Pinero "Thursday", ALS, 2 pp. (Box 15)
  - Richard Harding Davis to [John Kendrick] Bangs n.d., ALS, 1 p. with transcript (Box 15)
  - Richard Harding Davis to [Viola] Allen n.d., ALS, 4 pp. (Box 15)
  - Richard Harding Davis to Col. [________] Harvey n.d., ALS, 2 pp. (Box 15)
  - Richard Harding Davis to [Jeanette Leonard] Gilder n.d., ALS, 2 pp. (Box 15)
  - Richard Harding Davis to [______] Lincoln n.d., ALS, 1 p. (Box 15)
  - Richard Harding Davis to Walter S. MacPhail n.d., ALS, 1 p. (Box 15)
  - Richard Harding Davis to [Theodore} Roosevelt n.d., ALS, 1 p. (Box 15)
  - J[ames]; M[cNeil] Whistler to Richard Harding Davis n.d., ALS, 1 p. (Box 15)
  - Richard Harding Davis to City Editor of the Sunn.d., ALS, 1 p. (Box 15)
  - Richard Harding Davis to [Frances Wilson] n.d., ALS, 3 pp. (Box 15)
  - Richard Harding Davis to [_________] n.d., ALS, 1 p. (Box 15)
  - Richard Harding Davis to Robert [_____] n.d., ALS, 2 pp. (Box 15)
    With drawing at the bottom of the last page
- Photographs
  - Portrait of Richard Harding Davis n.d., Photograph, signed, 8.5 cm x 6.5 cm, mounted on board 8.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 15)
    Head and shoulders of Harding, 3/4 view, from a photograph by Pach Bros., NY.
  - Portrait of Richard Harding Davis [1893], Photograph, signed, 14.5 cm x 10 cm, mounted on board 16.5 cm x 10.5 cm (Box 15)
    Head and shoulders, full-face view, by Pach Bros., NY.
  - Two portraits of Richard Harding Davis [1893], Magazine photos, 7.5 x 5.5 cm (borders of ovals) (Box 15)
    Head and shoulders photographs that appear to be reproductions of the Pach Bros. full-face portrait.